there's been a bit of a stir, well the thing I don't
ha pasado una movida bueno la movida no
know if it's going to take a while when we saw the
sé si va a cortar aire cuando vimos el
video of a girl who exposed Yayo
vídeo de una chica que expuso al yayo
Gutierrez when all this happened with the
gutiérrez cuando pasó todo esto de la
cancellation of Rics there was a girl who
cancelación a rics hubo una chica que a
also came out took advantage of the opportunity
su vez salió aprovechó la oportunidad
from my point of view okay to
desde mi punto de vista vale para
cancel her there I am and she pans very well
cancelar ella allá yo y panea muy bien
Caribbeans and well he had already answered today I do
caribes y pues ya había contestado hoy
n't know why it took so long it
no sé por qué ha tardado tanto tiempo se
took like a month no like a month
ha tardado como un mes no como mejor mes
and a half to answer and it came out today on
y medio en contestar y ha salido hoy en
his twitter uploading this video that he
su twitter subiendo este vídeo que lo ha
uploaded to Vimeo
subido a vimeo
so let's see what the
así que vamos a ver lo que dice el
man says we don't have the right to listen to it
hombre no tenemos derecho a escucharlo
I'm on both sides no let's see both
estoy las dos partes no a ver las dos
sides of the coin let's see how he
caras de la moneda a ver de qué manera
expresses himself for example we saw we saw in his
se expresa por ejemplo vimos vimos en su
day both sides of the coin
día la dos caras de la moneda
rics hat ok and rick context as
sobrero de rics ok y rick contexto como
the very little cool ix that it would have been better if he
el poquísimo cool ix que mejor que se
had stayed street tics and now they've
hubiera quedado calle tics y ahora me
told me that rics has left the country is
han dicho de rics se ha ido del país es
that true or is it a lie I've lost a
eso verdad o es mentira l perdido un
little bit the book the story and well the
poquito el libro la historia y bueno el
video lasts  4 minutes
vídeo dura 4 minutos
4 points minutes to stuck a month and a
4 puntos minutos para pegado un mes y
half
medio
a month and a half to respond to your
un mes y medio para responder a su
cancellation
cancelación
you upload them to video that will not have
los subes a vídeo que no va a tener ni
the same impact
de coña la misma repercusión
and it lasts 4 minutes of the video I
y dura 4 minutos del vídeo
am not waiting for you to imagine how
no estoy esperando a que imaginen cómo
things have been around here although I
han estado las cosas por acá aunque
understand the different points of view
comprendo los distintos puntos de vista
that arose about my distancing
que surgieron sobre mi distanciamiento
on social networks during the last
en redes sociales durante las últimas
weeks that I left because I was
semanas que me fui porque me estaba
hiding that I did not want to show my face
escondiendo que no quería dar la cara
out of shame
por vergüenza
that dirty laundry is washed at home that I
que la ropa sucia se lava en casa que
was reserving in my personal life
estaba reservando en mi vida personal
because it is something that only I
porque es algo que solamente a mí me
should care about it was a bit of
debería de importar fue un tanto de las
both yes of course I had a lot I still
dos si por supuesto que tenía mucha sigo
feel a lot of shame nobody ever
sintiendo mucha vergüenza nadie nunca
wants to be involved in a scandal if
quiere verse envuelto en un escándalo si
the noise was another reason for the
el ruido fue otro motivo por la
commotion that was happening the
conmoción que estaba ocurriendo los
first few days I felt very overwhelmed and
primeros días me sentí muy abrumado y
far from helping contain things it
lejos de ayudar a contener las cosas
would have been to have said something like
hubiera sido de haber dicho algo como
yelling fire while standing in the middle of
gritar fuego estando parado en medio de
a fire and the main reason was my
un incendio y el motivo principal fue mi
concern for my mental state which
preocupación por mi estado mental que
was something that
era algo que
I do not like very much but I think he is
no me gusta mucho pero creo que me está
calling me to the treasury to see if now
llamando a hacienda a ver si ahora por
finally see if now they can  my fine
fin a ver si ahora consiguen mi multa
well I like to record a letter they
bueno me gusta grabar una carta que me
give me 2500 payments damn let's
dan 2500 pagos [__]
see if finally the one from the treasury was
a ver si por fin la de la hacienda era
eaten she
comida
hasn't checked it I bet anything that
no lo ha revisado apuesto lo que sea a
something is missing as always but well
que falta algo como siempre pero bueno
a little bit a little bit of victimhood I wasn't
un poquito un poquito victimismo no me
worried about my mental state guys
preocupaba mi estado mental chicos
and you're not worried about the other's mental state
y no te preocupa el estado mental de la
it's that we've already had minutes of video
otra es que ya llevamos minutos de vídeo
here thrown in the trash
aquí tirado a la basura
she owed me for a long
ella me debía desde hace un muy buen
time that I have abandoned previously
rato que he abandonado anteriormente
but for many it is a little more difficult to
pero para muchos es un poco más difícil
give space and now they know the reason for
dar espacio y ahora saben el porqué de
my absence I have already said this I would like to
mi ausencia ya he dicho esto quisiera
touch on your topics and why there is this
tocar tus temas y el porqué hay esto
absence or we knew about getting out of the
ausencia o sabíamos de quitarse del
way because you have the ring and I didn't know
medio porque tengas el aro y no sabía
what to say at that moment dude what are you going to
qué decir en ese momento churra que vas
say it's a
a decir
lie the treasury passed you the bill
es mentira la hacienda te pasó la cuenta
three thousand euros handsome thanks López hey
tres mil euros x guapo gracias lópez oye
even if you are not the treasury you can give me
aunque no seáis hacienda me podéis dar
money you can give me money okay below you
dinero me podéis dar dinero vale abajo
have a button that says join and I have
tenéis un botón que pone unirse y tengo
a special price for
un precio especial para lata
important cans and I want to try to be as
importantes y quiero intentar ser lo más
concise as possible as blunt as possible this
conciso posible lo más tajante esto no
is not gossip not to be when the end no  I'm going to
es chisme no estar when the end no voy a
contradict myself I'm going to contradict
contrariar me voy a contradecir a
people who have talked about me before I'm
personas que hayan hablado de mí antes
not going to point other people out in case that's
no voy a señalar a otras personas por si
what they were waiting for and this isn't
es lo que estaban esperando y esto no es
something that occurred to me today or how
algo que se me ocurrió hoy mismo o qué
good you are what good people you are
bueno eres qué buena gente eres tú
were goal today this attitude really
estaban gol hoy de esta actitud me
pisses
repatea
me off in my case if I had done that and they
yo en mi caso si hubiera hecho eso y me
put me down I would have said guys I
ponen hubiera dicho chavales
did it
lo hice
or you don't say anything okay like some people do
o no dices nada vale como hacen algunos
okay you shut up it marks you I still don't say anything
vale te callas te marca aún no digo nada
and I continue doing stupid things on the internet and
y sigo haciendo tonterías en internet y
acted like nothing but to say this
actuó como si nada pero para decir esto
about going around guys I apologize to
lo de andar chavales le pido perdón a
that person I'm so sorry I was when I
esa persona lo siento muchísimo estaba
was young adolescence I had
que era joven la adolescencia tenía la
adolescence my hormones were on
adolescencia me tenía las hormonas a
edge and I was hornier in a
flor de piel y estaba más caliente en un
whip lorea okay
latigazo lorea vale
you touched me and I did it it's hotter
tú me tocaba y hacía está más caliente
than they became mingo take thank you very much sorry sorry I
que se hicieron mingo toma muchas
promise I have everything
perdón perdón os prometo que tengo todo
deleted I promise I don't have anything
eliminado prometo que no tengo nada
saved I promise I haven't spread
guardado os prometo que no he difundido
anything I swear it was only for my
nada lo juro solamente era para mi
own enjoyment she was my girlfriend it was my thing
propio disfrute era mi novia era mi cosa
and I had it here for my pills I'm not
y lo tenía aquí para mis pastillas no lo
so sorry I really don't want to
siento muchísimo de verdad no quiero
think but saying this  It's been a
pensar pero decir esto ya hace a un
minute since the video and I haven't
minuto del vídeo y siendo no he
appeared for my mental health, I was taking
aparecido por mi salud mental tomaba
many thanks, welcome, he hasn't
muchas gracias bienvenido no ha
appeared because such, I have come to show my
aparecido porque tal he venido a dar la
face but this is not sal seo don't
cara pero esto no es sal seo no os
worry that I'm not going to throw [ __ ]
preocupéis que no le voy a tirar [__]
at anyone what are you going to throw [ __ ] at, he's an
a nadie a que le va tira [__] es
idiot and whoever has exposed you
[__] y a quien ha expuesto a ti
Caribbean thanks sweetheart it
caribe gracias corazón
's not something that I have been
no es algo que llevo días semanas
trying to get down on paper for days and weeks to be
intentando aterrizar en papel para
able to say first what happened with
poderlo decir primero lo que sucedió con
Hispania was an abuse of trust for
hispania fue un abuso de confianza a
personal benefit and it is something that I have
beneficio personal y es algo que yo he
known for a long time it was never
sabido desde hace mucho tiempo nunca fue
with the desire to hurt her although that
con el afán de herirla aunque en eso
falls on my immaturity and the mistake was not
recae en mi inmadurez y el error no fue
only having kept
solamente haber guardado un material
sensitive material from her without consulting her but
sensible de ella sin consultárselo sino
assuming that after things had been faced
asumir que después de haberse afrontado
the problem had been
las cosas el problema había quedado
fixed when one does not control what
arreglado cuando uno no manda sobre lo
another person could feel there
que otra persona pudiera llegar a sentir
are times when words are not
hay veces en que las palabras no son
enough to heal I recognize how bad it
suficientes para sanar reconozco lo mal
was and I recognize that at the time I
que estuvo y reconozco que en su momento
minimized it and it is something that should not be
lo minimice y es algo que no se debería
normalized however the
de normalizar sin embargo el apoyo
unconditional support that she received when it came
incondicional que recibió ella al salir
to light with  all of this highlights the
a la luz con todo esto deja en alto el
effort that is happening to change
esfuerzo que está sucediendo por cambiar
things in the environment, nobody deserves to
las cosas en el ambiente nadie merece
feel alone under these
sentirse solo bajo estas circunstancias
delicate circumstances and hopefully nobody ever has to be.
tan delicadas y ojalá y nadie nunca
Secondly, the privilege
tenga que estar lo segundo el privilegio
of being able to communicate anything and that
de poder comunicar cualquier cosa y que
thousands of people decide to give you their
miles de personas decidan brindarte su
attention is a double-edged sword. On the one
atención es un arma de doble filo por un
hand, misinformation causes
lado la desinformación causa
media contamination and that generates
contaminación mediática y eso genera
a lot of noise, nobody wins from this, but on the
mucho ruido nadie gana de esto pero por
other hand, transmitting a message with
otro lado transmitiéndose un mensaje con
the responsibility that it deserves can
la responsabilidad que se le debe puede
do something that positively affects
hacer algo que afecte positivamente a
others and that is what I want to conclude with
otros y es con lo que quiero concluir
because if I already have these minutes of
porque si ya cuento con estos minutos de
attention I feel that it is my
atención siento que es mi
responsibility to say the following: this
responsabilidad decir lo siguiente este
message is not something new, it is not something that
mensaje no es algo nuevo no es algo que
nobody has ever said before, but it is
nadie nunca haya dicho antes pero es
something worth emphasizing because
algo que vale la pena recalcar porque
by ignoring this, I have
por no hacer caso de esto es por lo que
found myself involved in this situation, which
me vengo envuelto en esta situación que
not only caused anguish to me but
no solamente me causó angustia a mí sino
to many people close to me directly and
a muchas personas cercanas directa e
indirectly. It is something that for a
indirectamente es algo que durante una
good part of my twenties I overlooked
buena etapa de mis veintes pasé por alto
between excesses and egocentrism in order to
entre excesos y egocentrismo por
try to cover up my insecurities, in order to
intentar maquillar mis inseguridades por
try to fill internal voids. respect
intentar llenar vacíos internos respeta
women, do not become a jerk, they are not
a las mujeres no se hace un patán no son
objects for  our
objeto para nuestro entretenimiento
sexual entertainment and it goes for any
sexual y va para cualquier identidad
sexual identity but now is when we have to
sexual pero ahora es cuando tenemos que
stop making the world feel let's
dejar de hacerle sentir al mundo
see how I say this without being
a ver como digo esto sin que se me
misunderstood okay let's see how I explain in
malinterprete vale a ver cómo explico
fact without anyone feeling offended
hecho sin que nadie se sienta ofendido
with my word without much text there won't be
con mi palabra sin mucho texto no habrá
much text in fact very little okay
mucho texto de hecho poquísimo vale
okay the point in which he has
está bien el punto en el que ha
recognized
reconocido
is ugly
está feo
I personally consider that there are
yo personalmente considero que hay cosas
much worse things okay
muchísimo peores vale
what he did is not good of course it's
no está bien lo que hizo por supuesto
not worth it but I consider that there are
que no vale pero considero que hay cosas
much worse things at the end of the day as far as
muchísimo peores al fin y al cabo hasta
I know correct me if I'm wrong he did not
donde yo sé corregirme si me equivoco no
distribute the images do not correct me if
distribuyó las imágenes no corregirme si
I'm wrong on this subject
me equivoco en este tema a este chaval
I know this guy very little
lo conozco bien poco
but he did
pero
not distribute the slab the same images
no difundió la losa las mismas imágenes
the same the
las mismas
same video calls nothing
las mismas videollamadas nada muchas
thank you very much the same half call he had
gracias la misma media llamada que tenía
with people who had sex over the
con gente que mantenía sexo a través de
internet well he takes some screenshots or
internet pues coge alguna captura o lo
whatever and then satiates his pages okay he
que sea y luego sacia sus páginas vale
had it in his private sphere well that's okay we are
lo tenía en su ámbito privado bueno eso
not going to say that it is good
está bien no vamos a decir que está bien
okay but obviously it is not the worst
vale pero evidentemente no es lo peor
okay in fact it is not bad but it is not
vale de hecho no es está mal pero no es
the worst
lo peor
okay you put it  I mean, one thing is
ya que tú te pongas o sea una cosa está
recognizing your mistake
en reconocer tu error
ok I did it wrong it was very ugly I did
ok lo he hecho mal ha estado muy feo
n't know that this girl
no sabía que esta chavala
I thought that when Enrique mobile
yo pensaba que cuando enrique móvil
thank you very much king and welcome
muchísimas gracias rey y bienvenido
welcome
bienvenido
I thought that when the girls
yo me me pensaba que cuando las chicas
I apologized well the girl so and so but she has
me disculpé pues la chica tal pero se ha
looted hurt that yes they arrived
saqueado dolida a que sí llegaron
then we are not talking about
entonces ya no estamos hablando de otra
something else Caribbean
cosa caribe
then we are talking about other people
entonces estamos hablando de otra gente
eye that is already a putt and yes model
ojo que ya es un putt y sí modelito
is that I stayed in what in the
es que yo me quedé en lo que en el vídeo
girl's video the girl what she says that he
de la chica la chica lo que dice que él
captures things and had them the step
captura las cosas y las tenía el paso
for her personal issue
para su tema personal
okay
vale
people have stopped a crime
la gente ha parado un delito
but anyway the case whatever it is
pero bueno el caso sea lo que sea
these to the other don't come now
sea estos al otro no vengan ahora
reality that Thalía of you have nothing
realidad de que thalía de no tienes nada
we are normalizing things we have to do
estamos normalizando cosas tenemos que
this do
hacer esto
not see birth rate is also that what
no ve natalidad es además que lo que a
calls my attention is that every time
mí me llama la atención es que cada vez
a cancellation happens and at least one
que pasa una cancelación y al menos una
person who is totally anti progressive and
persona que es totalmente anti progre y
who acts totally the
que actúa totalmente de todo lo
opposite how progressive acts think that
contrario cómo actúan progre piensa que
assuming the role of an ally
asumiendo el papel de un aliado
and their sins to be forgiven no
y sus pecados para ser perdonados no
one is going to believe you that now  suddenly
nadie te va a creer que ahora de repente
think like that and now suddenly they have
piense así y que ahora de repente tengan
mentalities
mentalidades
ask for forgiveness do not do it again
pide perdón no lo vuelva a hacer
compensates that person as having to
compensa esa persona como la tener que
compensate for something else
compensar a otra cosa
but does not fear the penalties we must
pero no teme las penalidades hay que hay
normalize we must cancel the one who is
que normalizar hay que cancelar al que
not what we
tal no
as men are risks
lo que como hombres somos son riesgos
even within consent there is
incluso dentro del consentimiento está
the obligation pull of the world that as men
la obliga tira del mundo que como
we are a risk
hombres somos un riesgo
that as men we are a risk
que como hombres somos un riesgo
gentlemen please give me a whip that
señores por favor darme un látigo que me
hits me hard on the back for being
pegue fuerte en la espalda por haber
born a man
nacido hombre
and the worst thing is not that but that he does not
y lo peor no es eso sino que no él no
think what he is saying
piensa lo que está diciendo
he does not think what he is saying do you
él no piensa lo que está diciendo
understand me
me entendéis
ask for forgiveness the [ __ ]
pide perdón la [__]
even within consent there is
incluso dentro del consentimiento está
the moral obligation not to hurt I
la obligación moral de no herir lo
extend it in the form of apologies to all
extiendo en forma de disculpas a todas
women obviously they are included
las mujeres obviamente están incluidas
who have been affected by my
que se han visto afectadas por mis
sexist and nefarious attitudes in
actitudes machistas y nefastas en los
recent years
últimos años
is that I am they will do machismo efe
es que soy harán machismo efe
or rather it is that you end up with machismo to
o sea es que te acaba un machismo a
anything if you are a [ __ ] pig
cualquier cosa si tú eres un [__] cerdo
that is not that we are machists already
eso no es que seamos machistas ya
machismo for me is that you treat
machismo para mí es que tú trates
the person differently for being a man and a
diferente a la persona por ser hombre y
woman okay when it is an aspect in which
mujer vale cuando es un aspecto en el
you  would have to treat with equality or
que le tendría que tratar con igualdad o
equity okay since I do things and
con equidad vale ya que yo haga cosas y
I value things differently if they
yo valoren las cosas diferentes si
come from a man than from
vienen por parte de un hombre que por
a woman okay but that you are
parte de una mujer vale pero que tú seas
disgusting does not mean that you are sexist because you
asqueroso no es que sean machista porque
can also be a disgusting person
puede ser también una persona asquerosa
and being a woman okay that you do what you
y ser una mujer vale que tú hagas lo que
have done is not sexist it is about being a
ha hecho no es de machismo es de ser un
filthy and disgusting being and on top of that if you
ser guarro y asqueroso y encima si lo
have shown it you have done something what a crime
has enseñado has hecho algo que delito
if you have done it it has already recorded
si tú lo has hecho ya ha grabado a
someone it has been captured while
alguien ha cogido captura mientras que
someone will show you their parts a
alguien te enseñará sus partes una
video call whatever you are dirty you
videollamada lo que sea eres un guarro
are here the hate
eres aquí los odios
but if you have shown it to other
pero si tú lo has enseñado a otras
people
personas
those crimes you can only do
esos delitos sólo lo puedes hacer
sexist not disgusting
machistas no asqueroso
and there are porn pages it
y hay páginas porno
is free dude porn nowadays you can
es gratís el porno tío hoy en día puedes
see whatever you want blonde big ass brunette
ver lo que quieras rubia culona morena
thin entrances whatever you like you
delgada entraditas lo que te guste lo
put it and find it for free so that
pones y lo encuentra gratis para que
when you get into trouble you
cuando te metes en líos
have to be an [ __ ] you
hay que ser [__]
have to be a real [ __ ] me
hay que ser [__] de verdad yo
when these things happen that I do not
cuando pasan estas cosas que no las
understand when they spread the UNDP it is about
entiendo cuando difunden pnud es de
people when  they record without
personas cuando graban sin
consent the people who do it for
consentimiento la gente que hace por
example what you hear out there that they put
ejemplo que se escucha por ahí que ponen
cameras in the bathrooms or that guys that
cámaras en los baños o que tíos que el
porn is free
porno es gratis
what a need there have
qué necesidad
been times when it has been
ha habido ocasiones en las que ha sido
disgusting and it is not something that I admit with
un asco y no es algo que admito con
pride I say it with great shame
orgullo lo digo con muchísima vergüenza
but sometimes it starts with small
pero a veces empieza por pequeños
changes and just as I can clarify that they are not
cambios y así como puedo aclarar que no
the same person the change is already
son la misma persona el cambio ya está
down the [ __ ] of the change of age
abajo la [__] del cambio de edad me
pisses me off the change
toca el huevo el cambio
what a change for the better the rest of things
qué cambio para mejor el resto de cosas
in life you have not done wrong
en la vida no has hecho mal
have been a pig that's it sorry sorry
haya sido un cerdo ya está perdón perdón
to the people affected
a las personas afectadas
if you have to pay something because as I tell you now
si tienes que pagar algo porque ya os
if someone sent you a photo, it does not give you the
si alguien te mandó una foto no te da
right to if someone shows you their
derecho a que si alguien te muestra su
body in a video call or sends you
cuerpo en una videollamada o te mando
the photos, it does not give you the right to
las fotos no te da derecho a que la
distribute it and by distributing not only
difunda y con difundir no solamente que
the band but also showing another
la banda sino que sea enseñar a otra
person that crime here and here in the
persona eso delito aquí y aquí en la
conca wow
conca guau
but since you tell me the change that
pero ya que me digas el cambio que
changes from a day of my life
cambia de un día de mi vida
that I was a decade ago I can also
que fui hace una década también puedo
recognize that there is a lot of internal work
reconocer que hay mucho trabajo interno
to do and I am with my finger
por hacer y estoy con el dedo bien
firmly on the line
puesto en el renglón
it is  doing because so canceled
lo está haciendo porque tan cancelado
point if you don't do it a piece of [ __ ] what
punto si no lo hace una [__] que
internal work are you going to call some
trabajo interno que vas a llamar a unos
bricklayers to get it built
albañiles para que te quede construido
jiang
jiang
me who has done it and could be I can't
yo que lo ha hecho y podría ser no puedo
really are superior to me
de verdad son superior a mí
superior sun has been invaded by the
sol superior ha sido invadido por el
spirit of wish my poor point
espíritu de wish mi punto pobre
and if what I'm saying can
y si esto que estoy diciendo puede
help many others much younger
ayudar a muchos otros mucho más jóvenes
or those people who still have
o aquellas personas que siguen teniendo
this erroneous mentality that I am
esta mentalidad errónea que estoy
correcting to not make this world a
corrigiendo a no hacer de este mundo un
place where a woman has to
lugar en el que una mujer tenga que
feel that she has to be careful
sentir que tiene que andarse con cuidado
at least it can help me feel
al menos me puede ayudar a mí a sentir
that I am putting a grain of sand in a
que estoy poniendo un granito en un
huge collective sack of consciousness
costal colectivo enorme de consciencia
that still needs to be filled
que todavía falta por llenar
this is the tone of the video literally
este es el tono del vídeo literalmente
this the tone of the video the video is has
este el tono del vídeo el vídeo es ha
been a pig and now I'm a league of
sido un cerdo y ahora soy una liga de
whipping myself for being men let's
fustigar me por ser hombres vamos a
paint them
pintarlos
the decorated benches please send
los bancos decorados por favor a enviar
like the wiki sebas let's put the box like
como el wiki sebas pongamos la caja como
what goes totally like whiskey
lo que se va totalmente como whisky se
walks let's put the skirts on the
pasea pongamos las faldas a las señales
traffic signs or rather you can't go from one
de tráfico o sea no se puede pasar de un
extreme to the other you don't think like that the kid
extremo a otro no piensas así el chaval
and nobody believes it normal nobody  You
y nadie se lo cree normales nadie se lo
believe it or what this is what many people do
cree o sea esto que hacen mucha gente
since giving a speech when they
desde de dar un discurso salida de
cancel it is absurd ask for
cuando lo cancelan es absurdo pide
forgiveness and do not do it again and pay what you
perdón y no lo vuelva a hacer y paga lo
have to pay if you have to pay
que tengas que pagar si tiene que pagar
someone something that's it
a alguien algo ya está
with this I am doing my bit you
que con esto estoy poniendo mi granito
are not an example for anyone has
de arena no eres un ejemplo para nadie
made a daycare that has grain of
ha hecho una guardería que ha granito de
sand is putting
arena está poniendo
that is incarcerated it is the grain of
que está encarcelado es el granito de
sand not the grain of sand to society is
arena no el grano de arena a la sociedad
given by people who do
se lo pone las personas que hacen las
things well from the heart and get out of them
cosas bien de corazón y salen de ellos
does things because they are intelligent and
hace las cosas porque son inteligentes y
realize how
se dan cuenta de cómo cambian los
times change and what is bad good not
tiempos y de qué es lo malo lo bueno no
because he cancels you so hit a host
porque te cancele tan pega una [__]
avoid that your actions today become
eviten que sus acciones hoy se vuelvan
your punishment tomorrow and the
su castigo de mañana y el
regret resentment and pain of
arrepentimiento resentimiento y dolor de
another person anticipate the consequences
otra persona anticipar las consecuencias
of our actions and not stumble again
de nuestros actos y no volver a tropezar
on the same stone is to mature think about
con la misma piedra es madurar piensen
what you do be conscience and help
lo que hacen tengan conciencia y ayuden
change that person who needs it let
a cambiar esa persona que lo necesita
this remain as a lesson for
que esto quede como una lección para
everyone
todos
but I am not like a lesson for
pero no estoy como que una lección para
the chapel or that this remains a
la capilla o que esto quede de una
lesson for all your eggs the lesson
lección para todos sus huevos la lección
for you [ __ ]  You don't have to
para ti [__] a mí no me tienes que
give me any lessons, I haven't done that, let
dar ninguna lección yo no he hecho eso
this be like an election for
que esto quede como una elección para
everyone and loot so so so comfortably and be like that at
todos y saquea tan tan tan agusto y esté
its best, shitty video
así en su punto vídeo de [__]
this has been a lesson for everyone but
este ha sido una lección para todos pero
what lesson are you going to give me
qué lección me vas a dar a mí
if I haven't done that,
si yo no he hecho eso
I really am amazed at the nerve that
yo de verdad la cara tan dura que tiene
people have, I'm shocked at the nerve that
la gente flipo con la cara que tiene la
people have, I'm shocked but like an
gente yo flipo pero como que una
election for all of us who are here, we have
elección para todos los que estamos aquí
n't done that, you have done,
no hemos hecho eso que tú has hecho
pieces of pig, I
pedazos de cerdo
have changed, I'm doing my bit
he cambiado estoy poniendo mi granito de
and this is a lesson for everyone but
y esto es una lección para todos pero
I'm dying but like a lesson
que yo me muero pero como una lección
for everyone
para todos
but everyone what lesson did I say to myself what is
pero que todos qué lección me dije a mí
really come on come on
lo que de verdad vamos vamos vamos
beta [ __ ] beta [ __ ] and that's it
beta [__] beta [__] y punto